{
    "subject": "resource/Demob_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "resource/United_Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "The country of the TV series Demob is the United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9182193875312805,
            "question": "Is Demob a British television series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6354516744613647,
            "question": "Is the TV series Demob likely to feature British humor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309801340103149,
            "question": "What country's television industry produced Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6109024286270142,
            "question": "In what country was Demob filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5699779987335205,
            "question": "Where is the TV series Demob set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5249289870262146,
            "question": "Could you tell me about the setting of the TV series Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4756181240081787,
            "question": "If you were watching Demob, what cultural cues might suggest it is British?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4536016583442688,
            "question": "What nationality are the characters in Demob likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41317346692085266,
            "question": "Is Demob a foreign production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22608277201652527,
            "question": "Demob's story probably draws from which culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country of the TV series Demob is the United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3362_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Demob a foreign production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3362_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality are the characters in Demob likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3362_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were watching Demob, what cultural cues might suggest it is British?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3362_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3362_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports this answer because all four documents mention that the TV series Demob was a British comedy-drama television series, which screened on ITV (a UK-based channel) and was set in the late 1940s and early 1950s."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about a British television series called \"Demob,\" which confirms that the country associated with this TV series is the United Kingdom."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}